# Natascha Vega

Bala-Cynwyd, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Natascha-Vega/df9c6fd6ba33c7d7

To find a position that will utilize my past experience and challenge me with the possibility for future growth.

To work with a company that has creative ambitions as it relates to employees as well as the industry.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

### KADUS COLOR LINE-TRAVELER

P&G Associates - February 2016 to Present

Responsibilities

Educator

Introduction/Education in salons, schools, product stores on how to use color line.

Lecture segments on the benefit of this line as well as showing and explaining techniques.

Social Media, Fashion shows, hair shows, all education on this brand.

### SCHWARZKOPF/THE BEAUTY INSTIUTE

Henkel - January 2015 to Present

Responsibilities

Master Educator

Educated all levels and oversees teaching educators, supported with curriculum role out of color and techniques. Role out of Makeup program and model program. Introduction to all

Cutting and styling techniques. Introduction to NAB and Todays class for lecture segments.

Over see Photo shoots and lay outs of new collection of styles.

# **Educator (part-time)**

Enzo Milano - 2014 to Present

Master Educator-Part Time

Handling schools, trade shows, private classes for salons on all educational matters

# Master Educator/Creative Leader

TONI&GUY HAIR ACADEMY - April 2012 to January 2016

Responsibilities

Master Educator/Creative Leader

Daily interaction with students and staff. Built lesson plans and teaching methods.

Graphics, videos, training of staff, created curriculums, advance training, class room training and growing of clinic floor

# **Toni Guy**

TI&GI - January 2011 to January 2013

Responsibilities

Director/Educational Director/FA Advisor/Admissions

Oversee all aspects for the operation of the school. Duties include, budget, training, teaching, teacher appraisals, financial aid, advertising, public relations, admissions department, handling all education departments as well as still educated in all areas

# VIDAL SASSOON/WELLA INTERNATIONAL-Educator/Educational Director

VISION BEAUTY ACADEMY - 2011 to 2012

# SUPERCUTS/PAUL MITCHELL/REDKEN-Director

REGIS - 1992 to 2011

Responsibilities

Director of Operations/Educator/Artistic Director

Growth of all educational departments, managing several salons, handled all training classes from cutting to advance color, handled all educational and operational departments

### owner

after hours hair salon - 2001 to 2009

### Distributor/Educator

IDEAL BEAUTY SUPPLY - 1990 to 1992

Responsibilities

Distributor/Educator/hands on classes on all product lines (Paul Mitchel, redken, Nixon, KMS,)

### **EDUCATION**

### **Master Educator License in Education**

The Vision Inst. - Ambler, PA 2011 to 2011

# Cosmetology

The Art of Beauty - New Orleans, LA 1989 to 1990

# Marketing in Education/Marketing

Cal State - Fullerton, CA 1985 to 1986

# School High Diploma

Pickering High School - Pickering, LA 1980 to 1985

# **SKILLS**

Natascha Vega has been in the industry since 1984, she has been part of the education process since 1992. She has worn many hats in this field, from salon owner to Artistic Director. Her establishments have been: Supercuts/Paul Mitchell/Redken-Artistic Director Vidal Sassoon-Educational Director in School format Toni & Guy-Educator, Educational Director, Creative leader, and then to Director of the academy. Schwarzkopf-Master Educator And now is a part of the KADUS family as an educator. Her passion has been Education with a twist, keeping herself current with always growing in many different ways. Working with the late Gorden Nelson has been one of her greatest passion's as well as her mentor to keep growing and sharing her knowledge. She has been part of the IBS shows with Enzo Milano as a freelance artist, she has conducted shows for HAIR World in Las Vegas and has been part of Signature events as well as Recertification's on her technical ability's yearly. 2001 she partnered up with fellow platform artist Scott Chestnut and created the AFTER HOURS HAIR SALON. Natascha is very current with her clients and has

a great relationship with Schools in her area. As well supports the community with Fashion Fest and Shows with local establishments: You will find Natascha now freelancing shows and conducting education classes. She currently growing her clients with the KADUS color and is excited to be part of the WELLA team. Classes that she most enjoyed: ABC CUTTING-VIDAL SASSOON-CA MUDD MAKEUP-NYC REDKEN MASTER COLOR CLASSES-NYC PAUL MITCHEL MASTER PROGRAM-MINN. CAO MAKEUP 3 DAY MASTER CLASSES-PHILADELPHIA KADUS COLOR 3 DAY EDUCATION CLASS-CA SCHARZKOPF MASTER COLOR CLASS-PHILADELPHIA MASTER CUTTING AND COLOR TECHNICAL CLASSES TONY & GUY-TEXAS WELLA COLOR TRAINIG-PHILADELPHIA HSA TRAINING-TEXAS "Hair is beauty & beauty is art, own it, love it, create it"

### **AWARDS**

# Cosmetology Educator of the year 2012

May 2012 Most Inspired Edcuator

# Manager of the Year 1996

January 1996 Most growth in all Salons

# Hair World 2006

January 2006 Most Creative stylist who ran Hair World in Las Vega

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **MUDD Trained**

Competed all segments to teach this program

### TIGI

Competed all segments to teach this program

# Schwarzkopf Edcuation

Competed all segments to teach this program

### **ACCSS Trained**

Competed all segments to teach this program

# **Kadus Education program**

Competed all segments to teach this program

# **Paul Mitchell Signature events**

Competed all segments to teach this program

### **HSA Training for Supercuts**

Competed all segments to teach this program

# **Redken Advance Color**

Competed all segments to teach this program